http://www.kuyper.edu/about-us/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Stay updated: Coronavirus/COVID-19 information.
Rolling Down - An ArtPrize Piece
RBI Graduate Celebrates 50 Years of Ministry in Oskaloosa, IA
2016 Faculty and Alumni Scholar Day
Presidential Transition Progresses to Application Review and Interviews
Year End Lunch 'N Learn
Presidential Transition Update - Kuyper College Retains Search Agency to Aid in Presidential Search
Malamiah Juice Bar
Kuyper Teams Garner Awards at MWest Challenge
Nemmers Interviewed at Lunch ‘N Learn
Spring Break!
Reformation Day Lecture Series
Former President, Nicholas Kroeze and Alumnus, Amanda Gilbert have work in ArtPrize Nine
ABHE Reaffirms Kuyper Accreditation
Inspiring Leaders Series Kicks Off with Mr. Nate VanderStelt
Youth Ministry Lunch 'N Learn welcomes Todd Tolsma
Kuyper Movie Night - Silence
Finding her haven of peace: Rebecca Laarman embracing working with youth in Tanzania
Dr. Carl Zylstra Appointed Interim President of Kuyper College
2018
The Top 10 Colleges and Universities in Michigan
Global Awareness and Advocacy Day
Kuyper College Unveils New Loan Repayment Assistance Program
Ready
Kuyper College and Madison Square Collaboration a “Mutual Blessing”
2019
Business in the U.S. National Parks
Make a Gift and Receive an Income for Life!
Ora et Labora: The Power of Staying
Kuyper Alumna Works with Troubled Youth in the Dominican Republic
Sophat Duch-My Story
Spring Arbor University’s & Kuyper College Students Benefit from Partnership
Kuyper College Triple Bottom Line Business Idea Contest
2019 Kuyper College Spring Celebration Gala
Academic Honors Convocation
Student Scholar Day
Trauma-Informed Care: Teaching. Applying. Consulting.
KuyperWorks Job Fair
Luminex, Kuyper College, and the Future of Theological Education
Kyle Kotrch Becomes Senior Pastor of Comstock Park Church
Kuyper College’s Social Work Program Ranked Top 10 Among Michigan Colleges
Kuyper College Now Able to Share Library Materials Statewide
Kuyper College Statement on Social Justice
Kuyper College Announces Plans for In-Person Instruction this Fall
Master Of Ministry Virtual Visit
Inspiring Leaders, Justin Giboney - "The AND Campaign: A Biblical Witness in Civic Engagement".
Kuyper Faculty - "Reflections on a Biblical Witness in Civic Engagement".
Lunch 'n Learn, Monique Carter from Center for Community Transformation.
Master of Ministry Virtual Visit
Consumer Information
Scholarship Celebration Event
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy will inform you on how your personal information is processed and used by Kuyper College. The following policies are only in effect for the webpages, online applications, forms and newsletters owned and operated by Kuyper College.
What Information we Collect and How it is Used
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's Internet Protocol Address (IP Address). When a visitor requests a page or file from the Kuyper website, our servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in website analytics software applications. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our servers do not automatically record the e-mail addresses of our website visitors.
When a visitor accesses and completes our online admissions application forms and online contact us forms, this data is collected and transmitted securely across the internet and housed in our administrative database for processing.
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails based on your request for information or for processing online applications submitted via our website.
Other Information About Online Privacy
The Kuyper College website contains many hyperlinks to third-party websites. In most cases, these links will open new browser windows. Kuyper College is not responsible for the content of the websites these links follow nor is Kuyper College responsible for the privacy practices of these websites.
Kuyper College does not share individual personal information you provide the college with these third party websites to which the Kuyper College website links. Please reference the privacy policies of these websites to determine their privacy practices.
Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online—for example through e-mail, web-based forms and applications as well as many additional ways—Kuyper College collects this information on its computing systems.
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
Consent to This Agreement
By visiting and using the Kuyper College website, you agree and consent to the collection and use of information by Kuyper College as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Additional Information and Questions
At any point during your visit with us, if you have any questions concerning your privacy, please feel free to contact the Kuyper Webmaster.
